Guide to the National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians (NABET-CWA) Records WAG.197
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians (NABET) Records
1958-2009
1970-1990
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians
WAG.197
19 Linear Feet 19 records cartoons and two oversize flat file folders.
2 websites in two archived websites.
National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians (now known as NABET-CWA) represents professional and non-professional employees in the broadcast industry. Initially founded in the mid-1930s as a company union for the National Broadcasting Company, it has grown to represent over 10,000 workers in many bargaining units. In 1951, NABET joined the Congress of Industrial Organizations. Some internal disputes in the 1960s led the union to give greater autonomy to local networks and affiliates, a concession that has contributed to the present structure of the organization. NABET led two major strikes against the national networks, American Broadcasting Company in 1977 and National Broadcasting Company in 1987. In 1994 the union merged with the Communications Workers of America to become NABET-CWA. The collection contains bargaining and organizing notes, websites, convention records, materials from the merger conference with the Communications Workers of America, and strike materials.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians - Communications Workers of America, in 2001. The accession numbers associated with this gift are 2001.042 and 2001.050.
The accession numbers 1990.009 and 1990.010 are also associated with this collection.
https://www.nabetcwa.org/ was initially selected by curators and captured through the use of The California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service in 2009 as part of the Labor Unions and Organizations (U.S.) Web Archive. In 2015, these websites were migrated to Archive-It. Archive-It uses web crawling technology to capture websites at a scheduled time and displays only an archived copy, from the resulting WARC file, of the website. In 2018, https://www.nabetcwasports.org/ was added to the web archives. The accession number associated with these websites are 2019.100.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
The predecessor union of NABET, the Association of Technical Employees (ATE), was founded in 1934. The National Broadcasting Company (NBC) formed the ATE as a company union, in an effort to prevent their employees from being organized by the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW). The ATE would not stay under NBC control for long. It began an energetic organizing campaign, and in 1940 changed its name to the National Association of Broadcast Engineers and Technicians (NABET).
During this period, NBC owned two national networks, designated Red and Blue. In the early 1940s the Federal Communications Commission ordered NBC to divest some of its holdings, and NBC sold the Blue network, which soon became the American Broadcasting Company (ABC). NABET retained the right to represent the professional employees of ABC.
In 1951, in the midst of a jurisdictional dispute with the IBEW and looking for allies, NABET joined the Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO). The CIO gave NABET a charter to organize all broadcast industry employees. To reflect this broadening of representation, the union changed its name to the National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians and began to organize non-professional workers.
Shortly after its affiliation with the CIO, the NABET-IBEW dispute came to a head over organizing the Columbia Broadcasting Company (CBS). The CBS disagreement was brought before the National Labor Relations Board (NLRB). The Board ruled in favor of the IBEW, which was given authority to organize CBS technical employees.
In 1967 the Hollywood and New York City locals led a fight to strengthen the authority and autonomy of local NABET organizations. This dispute nearly destroyed the union, but resulted in constitutional changes that increased the influence and independence of the network locals.
NABET led ABC national network employees through a strike in 1977. Again in 1987, the NABET workers struck, this time on behalf of the NBC national network. Throughout the late 1970s to the mid-1990s NABET continued to organize local networks and affiliate stations.
In 1993 NABET became affiliated with the Communications Workers of America (CWA). In 1994 NABET and CWA held a conference on the possibility of solidifying their affiliation with a formal merger. The conference was a success, and in 1994 NABET merged with CWA. The union once again changed its name, becoming NABET-CWA. NABET-CWA currently represents over 10,000 workers in the broadcast industry.
Scope and Content Note
This colllection includes bargaining files of small and individual-station broadcasting companies, assorted records of the 1994 merger conference with CWA, NABET convention records 1968-1990, correspondence of the International Secretary-Treasurer and Regional Vice-Presidents, NABET Severance Benefit Trust records, and correspondence with the OPEIU. Also included are the bargaining files of the American Broadcasting Company and the National Broadcasting Company, including minutes, proposals, correspondence, negotiation notes, and assorted files from the ABC strike of 1977, the NBC strike of 1987, and the union's websites. Materials pertaining to local affiliates includes the bargaining and organizing files of local and affiliate stations.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically. The files are grouped into three series, one of which is arranged into subseries:
Series I: General Files, 1958-1995
Series II: Bargaining Files, 1959-1995
Subseries II:A: National Networks, 1959-1988
Subseries II:B: Local Affiliates, 1974-1995
Series III: Archived Websites, 2009-ongoing
Take Down Policy
Archived websites are made accessible for purposes of education and research. NYU Libraries have given attribution to rights holders when possible; however, due to the nature of archival collections, we are not always able to identify this information.
If you hold the rights to materials in our archived websites that are unattributed, please let us know so that we may maintain accurate information about these materials.
If you are a rights holder and are concerned that you have found material on this website for which you have not granted permission (or is not covered by a copyright exception under US copyright laws), you may request the removal of the material from our site by submitting a notice, with the elements described below, to the repository email.
Please include the following in your notice: Identification of the material that you believe to be infringing and information sufficient to permit us to locate the material; your contact information, such as an address, telephone number, and email address; a statement that you are the owner, or authorized to act on behalf of the owner, of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed and that you have a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; a statement that the information in the notification is accurate and made under penalty of perjury; and your physical or electronic signature. Upon receiving a notice that includes the details listed above, we will remove the allegedly infringing material from public view while we assess the issues identified in your notice.
Financial records; Proceedings.; Memorandums.; Membership lists.; Ballots.; Rosters.; Proposals.; Radio broadcasting |x Employees |x Labor unions |z Canada.; Transcripts.; Radio broadcasting |x Employees |x Labor unions |z United States.; Television broadcasting |x Employees |x Labor unions |z Canada.; Television broadcasting -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Agreements.; Collective labor agreements.; Minutes (administrative records); Constitutions.; Correspondence.; Field notes.; Contracts; Legal documents.; Communications Workers of America; National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians; American Broadcasting Company; Office and Professional Employees International Union; National Broadcasting Company; National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians
- Series I: General Files, 1958-1995
  - Cable News Network (CNN): Authorization Cards, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Capital Center Area, Washington DC, 1984-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Communications Workers of America (CWA) Conference: Appointments, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CWA Conference: Ballots, By-Laws, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - CWA Conference: Ballots, Officers, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - CWA Conference: By-Law Changes (originals), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - CWA Conference: Candidates, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - CWA Conference: Cash Advances, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CWA Conference: Committee Minutes, Delegate Lists, Memos, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - CWA Conference: Coordination Meetings, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - CWA Conference: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CWA Conference: Delegate Certificates, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - CWA Conference: Delegate Confirmations, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - CWA Conference: Delegate Registration, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CWA Conference: Delegates, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CWA Conference: Membership List (I), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - CWA Conference: Membership List (II), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - CWA Conference: Membership List (III), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - CWA Conference: Membership Verifications, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - CWA Conference: Petitions, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - CWA Conference: Production/Coordination Notes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - CWA Conference: Proposed Amendments to By-Laws, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - CWA Conference: Speakers/Press Releases, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - CWA Conference: Transcripts (I), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - CWA Conference: Transcripts (II), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - CWA Conference: Vote Count Report, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Convention, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Convention, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Convention, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Convention, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Convention: Expenses, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Convention, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Convention: Delegates, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Convention, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Convention: Constitution Amendment Ballots, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Convention: Constitution and By-Laws, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Convention: Constitution Committee Report, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Convention: Correspondence (I), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Convention: Correspondence (II), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Convention: Correspondence (III), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Convention: Delegate Rosters and Certificates, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Convention: Financial Records, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Convention: International Secretary-Treasurer and Vice-President Ballots, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Convention: Planning, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Donahoe/Mathis, re: fines, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Electronic Race Patrol, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - International Secretary-Treasurer (IST): Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - IST: Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - IST: Correspondence, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - IST: Correspondence, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - IST: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - IST: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - IST: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - IST: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - IST: Correspondence, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - IST: Correspondence, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - IST: Correspondence, Jan 1993-Jun 1993 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - IST: Correspondence, Jul 1993-Dec 1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Local 11-Local 53 Dispute, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Mark Video (I), 1979-1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Mark Video (II), 1979-1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Mobile Video Services (I), 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Mobile Video Services (II), 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - NABET Severance Benefit Trust (NSBT), 1962-1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - NSBT: Correspondence, 1972-1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - NSBT: Fiduciary Insurance, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - NSBT: Legal Issues, 1978-1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - NSBT: Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU) Correspondence, 1958-1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - NSBT: Participants who have withdrawn from plan, 1964-1976 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - NSBT: Plan, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - NSBT: Trust and Plan Documents, 1974-1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - NSBT: Trustees, 1972-1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU): Contract Correspondence, 1959-1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - OPEIU: Employment, Resignations, Personnel, 1958-1993 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - OPEIU Plan, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - OPEIU: Severance Fund Correspondence, 1958-1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - OPEIU: Severance Plan Trust, 1977-1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - RCA Records (I), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - RCA Records (II), 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Regional Vice-President (RVP): Elections, 1978-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - RVP: Petitions, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - RVP: Region 1-Correspondence, 1981-1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - RVP: Region 2-Correspondence, 1986-1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - RVP: Region 3-Correspondence, 1981-1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - RVP: Region 4-Correspondence, 1981-1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - RVP: Region 5-Correspondence, 1976-1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - RVP: Region 6-Correspondence, 1980-1991 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - RVP: Region 11-Correspondence, 1983-1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - RVP: Region 11-Election Dispute, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - RVP: Vernick Challenge, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - RKO General, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - RKO General Certification, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Sherman Grinberg Film Libraries, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Wayne State University, 1972-1980 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Series II: Bargaining Files, 1959-1995
  - Subseries II:A: National Networks, 1959-1988
    - American Broadcasting Company (ABC): Agreement, Draft (I), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - ABC: Agreement, Draft (II), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - ABC: Agreement, Draft (III), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - ABC: Agreement, Master, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - ABC: Agreement, Master, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - ABC: Bulletins, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - ABC: Bulletins, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - ABC: Correspondence (I), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - ABC: Correspondence (II), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - ABC: Correspondence (III), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - ABC: Labor Relations Board, 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - ABC: Memoranda of Agreement (I), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - ABC: Memoranda of Agreement (II), 1971 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - ABC: Memoranda of Agreement, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - ABC: Minutes (I) (with NBC also), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - ABC: Minutes (II) (with NBC also), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - ABC: Minutes (III) (with NBC also), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - ABC: Minutes, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - ABC: Minutes, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - ABC: Minutes (I), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - ABC: Minutes (II), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - ABC: Minutes (I), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - ABC: Minutes (II), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - ABC: Minutes (III), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - ABC: Negotiations (I), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - ABC: Negotiations (II), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - ABC: Negotiations, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - ABC: Negotiations-Desk Assistants (I), 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - ABC: Negotiations-Desk Assistants (II), 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - ABC: Negotiations-Proposals and Minutes (I) (with NBC also), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - ABC: Negotiations-Proposals and Minutes (II) (with NBC also), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - ABC: Negotiations-Proposals and Minutes (III) (with NBC also), 1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - ABC: Proposals, Company (I), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - ABC: Proposals, Company (II), 1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - ABC: Proposals, Company (I), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - ABC: Proposals, Company (II), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - ABC: Proposals, Company (I), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - ABC: Proposals, Company (II), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - ABC: Proposals, Company, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - ABC: Proposals/Contracts Master File (I), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - ABC: Proposals/Contracts Master File (II), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - ABC: Proposals/Contracts Master File (III), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - ABC: Proposals/Contracts Master File (IV), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - ABC: Proposals/Contracts Master File (V), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - ABC: Proposals/Contracts Master File (VI), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - ABC: Proposals, Counter-Company, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - ABC: Proposals, Counter-Company (I), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - ABC: Proposals, Counter-Company (II), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ABC: Proposals, Counter-NABET, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - ABC: Proposals, Counter-NABET (I), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - ABC: Proposals, Counter-NABET (II), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - ABC: Proposals, NABET (with NBC also), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - ABC: Proposals, NABET (I), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - ABC: Proposals, NABET (II), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - ABC: Proposals, NABET (III), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - ABC: Proposals, NABET (I), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - ABC: Proposals, NABET (II), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - ABC: Proposals, NABET (III), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - ABC: Proposals, NABET (I), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - ABC: Proposals, NABET (II), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - ABC: Strike, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - ABC: Strike (I), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - ABC: Strike (II), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - ABC: Strike-Complaints/Answers, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - ABC: Strike-Correspondence (I), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - ABC: Strike-Correspondence (II), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - ABC: Strike-Court Cases: Illegal Picketing, Unfair Labor Practices, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - ABC: Strike-Negotiations (I), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - ABC: Strike-Negotiations (II), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - ABC: Strike-Negotiations (III), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - ABC: Strike-Negotiations (IV), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - ABC: Strike-Negotiations, Dailies, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - ABC: Strike-Pennsylvania Strikebreaker Law, Injunctions and Petitions, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - ABC: Strike-Picketing, Daytona International Speedway, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - ABC: Strike-Picketing, Los Angeles Dodgers, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - ABC: Strike-Picketing, Pimlico Raceway/Maryland Jockey Club, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - ABC: Strike-Picketing, Washington DC (Hilton Hotel), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - ABC: Strike-Picketing, Washington DC (Hyatt Regency Hotel), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - ABC: Strike-Picketing, Washington DC (International Inn), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - ABC: Strike-Picketing, Washington DC (Mayflower Hotel), 1977 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - ABC: Strike-Remote Picketing, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - ABC: Strike-San Francisco, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - ABC: Strike-Settlement Agreement Proposals, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - ABC: Strike-Subpoenas, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - ABC: Strike-Tulsa, Oklahoma, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - ABC: Strike-Union Proposals, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - National Broadcasting Company (NBC): Agreements (I), 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - NBC: Agreements (II), 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - NBC: California Superior Court-Thomas Montague Hall Case, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - NBC: Employee Rosters (I), 1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - NBC: Employee Rosters (II), 1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - NBC: Employee Rosters (III), 1987 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - NBC: Federal Communications Commission (FCC)-Decision and Consent Decree, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - NBC: Graphic Artists (I), 1981-1984 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - NBC: Graphic Artists (II), 1981-1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - NBC: Lock Out, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - NBC: Negotiations (I), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - NBC: Negotiations (II), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - NBC: Negotiations (with ABC also) (I), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - NBC: Negotiations (with ABC also) (II), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - NBC: Negotiations (with ABC also) (III), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - NBC: Negotiations (with ABC also) (IV), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - NBC: Negotiations (I), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - NBC: Negotiations (II), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - NBC: Negotiations (III), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - NBC: Negotiations (IV), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - NBC: Negotiations (I), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - NBC: Negotiations (II), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - NBC: Negotiations (III), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - NBC: Proposals, Company (I), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - NBC: Proposals, Company (II), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - NBC: Proposals, Company (III), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - NBC: Proposals, Company (I), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - NBC: Proposals, Company (II), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - NBC: Proposals, Company (III), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - NBC: Proposals, Counter-Company (I), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - NBC: Proposals, Counter-Company (II), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - NBC: Proposals, Union (I), 1970 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - NBC: Proposals, Union (II), 1970 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - NBC: Proposals, Union (III), 1970 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - NBC: Proposals, Union (IV), 1970 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - NBC: Proposals, Union (I), 1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - NBC: Proposals, Union (II), 1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - NBC: Proposals, Union (I), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - NBC: Proposals, Union (II), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - NBC: Settlement Agreement, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - NBC: Strike-Attorney Invoices, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - NBC: Strike-Civil Suit, Refusal of Income Savings Plan for Union Members, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - NBC: Strike-Conference Calls, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - NBC: Strike-Contempt Proceedings-New York District Court, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence (I), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence (II), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence (III), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence (IV), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence (V), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence, Local 11, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence, Local 31, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence, Local 42, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence, Local 51, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence, Local 53 (I), 1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence, Local 53 (II), 1987 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence, Nolan, James, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence, Politicians, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - NBC: Strike-Correspondence with Other Unions, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - NBC: Strike-Defense Fund Vouchers, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - NBC: Strike-District Court Case, Local 53, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - NBC: Strike-Expenses, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - NBC: Strike-Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS), 1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - NBC: Strike-Insurance Payments, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 10)